(Sheldon:)I don't...
(Leonard:)That's really two different questions.
I'm not...
(Leonard:)Sheldon, we have to go.
(Sheldon:)Boy, you're wound awfully tight
for a man who just had sexual intercourse.
All right, well, I'll talk to you later.
But I am so happy for you, Leonard.
(Penny:)Thank you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Leonard:)What did she mean, she's happy for me?
(Leonard:)Is she happy because I'm seeing someone
or because she thinks I'm happy?
(Leonard:)Because anyone who cared for someone
would want them to be happy...
(Leonard:)...even if the reason for their happiness
made the first person unhappy.
(Leonard:)You know, because the second person,
though happy...
(Leonard:)...is now romantically unavailable
to the first person.
Do you realize I may have to share
a Nobel Prize with your booty call?
You know what?
(Leonard:)I'm being ridiculous.
But who cares what Penny thinks?
Leslie is a terrific girl.
She's attractive. We like each other.